[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] Hi, Hemal. How are you?
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] I'm doing good, Nicola. Thank you so much for inviting me for beer.
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] Yeah, I think we should start with a toast, right?
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: audio_event] (laughs)
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] Yeah. Cheers.
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] Cheers.
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] Cheers.
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] Ah, nice beer.
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] Nice one.
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] So...
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] So, yeah, how, how do we met? We met yesterday for the first time in real life.
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] Yes.
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] And now we are here talking-
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] ... and spending some time together.
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] Yes.
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] That's so cool.
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] Thank you so much, uh, for this, uh, invitation for this interview.
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] Mm-hmm.
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] Yesterday, we had an amazing, uh, n8n starter session in Barcelona. It's an official tour from
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] n8n across seven countries, Europe and US. Um,
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] it was great to meet you.
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] Yeah. Thank you. And there were so many people. The vibes were, were so great.
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] Yes.
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] And, and I was actually... We were talking about this before, right? I was inspired by hearing your
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] story. And apart from all the cool stuff that you do with n8n, automations, AI, th- which is
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] amazing, but what I really like and, um,
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] relate to you was, like, your motivation behind all of this, like, why you are doing this.
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] Sure.
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: audio_event] (laughs)
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] Why you are doing this?
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] Thank you. Thank you so much. Yeah, uh, to be honest, the reason I'm, uh, I'm
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] doing all this AI education, especially with the
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] monthly, um,
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] free workshops and all the n8n ambassador program, uh, is because, uh, I started
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] learning coding when I was, like, 16 year old or 15 years old, um, in a developing country, um,
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] or even underdeveloped as a refugee in Pakistan. Um,
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] and the reason that I was exposed to this, uh, computer programming education early on in my life, despite having
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] very mediocre lifestyle or, or maybe even a poor lifestyle I would say,
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] uh, that it, uh, early exposure to, to AI... not AI, but, like, coding,
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] brought me today here where I am. Otherwise, I might have ended up in a totally different, uh, circumstance in
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] my life, financially speaking, educationally, and also lifestyle-wise. And I want to
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] pay back to the community and, and, and teach a lot of, uh, 16 years old kids around the world,
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] whether this be in India, Pakistan, Afghanistan, Bangladesh, uh, South America, wh- wherever it is. Like, uh, there are a
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] lot of developing countries with internet connections that they can play a YouTube video. And if get, they get, uh,
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] one of my YouTube videos, uh, and they, they learn how to build, uh, something, I,
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] I would be really, really happy. And it's just the start of the journey. I'm-
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] Yeah, just the beginning.
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] ... way far away from that
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] first million
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] 16 year old kids who will, uh, who will learn from my content.
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] Mm-hmm.
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] Yeah.
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] I see. I s-... That's, like, really the best mission. And
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] I remember yesterday you were saying that you're already hearing back stories from, from kids in, in India or, or
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] somewhere else that-
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] Yeah.
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] ... writes you, right?
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] Saying, "I, I watched your video, and it was so helpful, so clear, like this, uh, eight hours long
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] video."
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] Yeah.
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] "And I can just followed it, put in, uh, in, in the work, and help someone in, in my community,
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] my neighborhood, the, the shop nearby, the, the, um, the doctor, and-"
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] Yes.
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] "... help them right away thanks to code and AI."
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] Yes, uh, that-
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] That's super cool.
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] ... uh, that's amazing. Like, each time I get these
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] either shout-outs on LinkedIn that people
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] learned something, did something, or, or they send me a DM, they say like, "Thank you so much for this
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] tutorial you're putting in." It's, it's, um, kind of the fuel I need in order to produce more and more
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] and more. Uh, and, and this kid from India sent me a message that he started building this little voice
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] AI agent. And, uh, many, many more like those examples come.
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] Mm-hmm.
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] And it's, as I said, it's just the start. I, I started my journey literally a few months ago, and
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] it's gonna get, uh, I think, bigger and bigger. I'm, uh-
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] It's moving pretty fast.
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] I'm so passionate about this.
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] Yeah.
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] Yeah.
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] And, and then I, I think you have just, uh, started a company in the last month-
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] ... or last few months.
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] Yeah.
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] Right? What, what's your, um, uh, goal with that? Or what do you... what are you cooking now?
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] So, with this new company, Avinai, um, Chris and I are, uh,
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] building AI agents, or kind of
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] in a metaphorical way, we are reimagining work. Uh, we believe that in the near
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] future, the work as we know it will change. And we at Avinai are at the fore- at the forefront
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] of reimagining how work is done. Uh, and I, I believe with this agentic workflows, with AI
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] agents, and with AI automation, we can definitely rethink about how work should be done, because a lot of work
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] is repetitive. And especially in enterprise level, there, there are a lot of automation, uh, opportunities that
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] even low-hanging fruits could be like automating, copy-pasting from one system to another system that ca-... that could be done,
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] uh, anyways by literally gluing two APIs together. But now, if you find, like, an horizontal use case where
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] across multiple systems...... an AI agent can have an
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] a- access to all those tools
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] and
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] perform those actions across those tools. Uh, it will create an enormous, um, value for
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] that particular organization. Uh, and I think it's just the start. It's gonna get bigger.
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] So, you, you think, uh, that it's like rethinking
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] the, the way of working with AI? How do you
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] help the company, uh, a client, a, a company, uh, go about it, right?
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] So, yeah. The, the, the reason that we
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] want to kind of like bring this visibility of reimagining or rethinking how work is done is
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] because until now, we have been using computers in a way to
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] enable us to do our job better. And now, computers can do the job. So therefore, it's
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] time that we have to rethink or reimagine how work is done.
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] It's not that we're gonna... for example, Excel. Excel was very good to do calculations, but enabled us to do
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] better calculation. Now, let's take an example of an AI agent that is doing invoices.
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] It's gonna do the reconciliation for you. It's gonna do the booking for you. It's gonna do the travel expenses,
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] the r- uh, the payroll and everything else for you. So, you have to, at the principal level, rethink
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] and reimagine how work should be done.
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] Yeah.
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] And that's where we, we play, uh, uh, an extremely, um, crucial role because we not only bring
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] in the, um,
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] the empowering, uh,
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] capabilities, but also from the day one, we, we bring in the discovery phase to it, uh, with workshops
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] initially, and then enablement, uh, sessions and development sessions and maintenance and, and so on and so forth.
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] Yeah.
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] So, kind of like a 360-degree service company.
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] 'Cause I, I, I hear more and more people saying this, that with, with AI, it's a lot about people
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] right now.
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] Like,
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] the tool or the
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] brain of AI is already extremely good to do most of the work.
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] Mm-hmm.
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] But the issue is how people use it, or
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] the famous AI adoption that is not a- as easy, especially the, the bigger the company. Uh, so there
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] is
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] some help there needed, right?
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] Uh, yeah. The AI adoption right now, um, especially the, the, the blockers in SMEs and-
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] Mm-hmm.
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] ... big companies, uh, can be understandable because it's not so high and, and the reason is because
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] usually these AI, um, models could hallucinate. So, we have guardrails, but they are so
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] young. Like, every single project that you can pick that can, um, enable, uh, an
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] AI agent to reduce the hallucinations and put the right guardrails, those projects by themselves are like three, four, five,
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] six months old. Now,
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] the enterprise is not adopting it
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] yet, uh, because of the immaturity of those projects. But they're developing so fast that
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] I believe in six months,
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] they will be enterprise-ready.
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] Mm-hmm.
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] But the... on the other side of the spectrum,
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] there are certain things that can be used today in, uh, enterprise. Uh, for example, let's take an,
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] uh, a simple workflow in n8n. Um, by the way, Avanade is an n8n expert company.
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] We do n8n workshops and n8n, uh,
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] implementation for enterprises.
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] So, let's take an n8n workflow. You, you do n8n workflows for companies.
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] You already know how easy it is or how secure it is to, to put an n8n workflow that
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] does, let's say, ticket cal- classification. Enterprises get these support tickets in thousands.
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] Mm-hmm.
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] And usually, there's a workflow or a process that a human being
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] has access to an inbox. Let's say help at Allianz or support at Allianz.de, for
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] example. And, and they decide, okay, this label goes to it, this label goes to it, this one goes to
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] that department, this one goes to that department. So, there's a lot of labeling and, and, and routing and things
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] that today's AI can do it with a very high degree of certainty.
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] Yeah.
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] Can be done with today's AI. And also, I, I teach a lot about EU AI Act in my, uh,
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] workshops.
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] Mm-hmm.
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] Happy to discuss about that more. I don't want to go on a monologue.
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: audio_event] (laughs)
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] Sorry, uh, like this kind of thing.
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] Yeah, no, no worries. Go on.
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] But, but, like, these, uh, compliance s- or legal side effect can also be done with n8n and, and with
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] the current AI tech stack we have. So, from one side, high-risk, um,
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] applications should not be done with AI yet. But in the next six months to one year, it's possible. Uh,
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] on the other side, uh, low-risk, um, applications, uh, can be done today with AI. And I think, uh, the
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] enterprise is just catching up and it's the best time to provide these services.
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] Yeah. I think that
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] there is,
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] there are, as y- as you said, already ways to, to figure out the legal and the, the other kind
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] of, of things, right? The, the formalities. But if a company wants to do it and puts in the right
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] effort, it's...... working, right?
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] Yeah.
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] You can really do that.
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] Yes.
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] And you have, you have said a few things about enterprise and big companies. How do you see, uh, right
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] now the- the use cases or the application for, uh, small companies, medium companies that have
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] no idea of how to use it? They want to do something with it, but they don't know where to
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] start. Like, they are overwhelmed.
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] Um,
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] eh, s- especially small businesses, like for example, this, uh, restaurant, beautiful restaurant, a lot of
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] customers. If they start... The- the owner of this restaurant starts thinking about implementing an AI agent in
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] their workflow, they are the right people to identify which process is so repeated. Don't-
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] Yeah.
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] Uh, kind of like if I was building AI agents for small restaurants, uh, not chains, small restaurants, I would
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] go and talk to them, and I would not tell them that A- AI agents can do this and that.
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] I wouldn't show them N8N workflows. I wouldn't try to sell all the bells and whistles of AI agents. I
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] would go and talk to them, and I would say, "Can you show me which workflow do you do? Like,
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] what is the most repetitive workflow that you do?" And most probably, you will find a workflow that is doable
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] with the current AI agent's workflow automation, uh, I mean, AI, uh, automation.
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] And then you pick one niche that is so repetitive, like every day they do the same thing again and
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] again. For example, they take these slips, they put it in this, like, big, uh,
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] pin. It's a pile of slips, and then they kind of like reconcile it somewhere, or key punch it, or
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] scan it, or do something with it.
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] Mm-hmm.
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] That's doable. Like, in this N8N starter, uh, workshop, one of the workflows is receipt scanning.
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] Perhaps they need this, uh, receipt scanning. And you- you- you know how to do it. It's so simple.
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] Yeah, it's simple.
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] Uh, and then if you can automate that one workflow for them, that they scan a receipt with Google Drive,
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] it goes and sits there on a, as a PDF, and it does an entry on Google Sheets. And it
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] is perhaps also connected with their POS, their point of sales.
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] Uh, and- and then maybe it does a s- uh, a push notification with some summaries every hour to the
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] owner
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] from all the branches that he has on Slack.
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] Yeah.
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] This kind of a workflow is already doable. And then you, you do it perfectly for one restaurant, and then
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] you start going around in Barcelona city, and then you keep selling it to the next restaurants. I think the
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] ROI for this, for let- even if you sell it for a thousand euros,
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] and it takes you one hour to install it. Uh, let's say another
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] two hours in total accumulated across all your sales pipelines
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] per client. So in three hours, you're making a thousand euros. It's an extremely luc- lucrative business. Um,
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] now imagine if you can
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] sell more of this by hiring people. On the other side, it's also lucrative for the business because something that
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] they used to do with hand, with human brain, now can be done with AI. So the ROI for the
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] restaurant is positive already. A thousand euro is nothing for a restaurant to put a kind of tech stack that's
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] frontier and it's agentic, it's-
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] it's top-notch, uh, quality. And also you can provide support with that 1,000 euros. Maybe you- you put another package
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] on the top, 300 euros per year for- for unlimited support.
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] Yeah.
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] You can imagine like a workflow like that, how much support it needs. But 300 euro is like 30 euros
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] subscription per month.
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] Mm-hmm.
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] So you build yourself a service business that pays upfront some money, and then on a- on a- on a
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] monthly basis, a recurring revenue. And also, when you get into a restaurant, then it's not one workflow. Next time
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] they need another workflow, another two, three thousand euro-
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] Yeah.
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] ... another two, three thousand euros.
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] Okay.
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] So that way you build yourself a- a lucrative ag- AI automation agency business.
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] Okay. Okay. And
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] okay, so you- you have touched
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] many points that
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] are like now becoming buzzwords and because of the hype around AI agents, blah, blah, blah, all these things
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] that
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] we always talk about it. But most people outside
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] our tech bubble don't know yet what does it mean. So if I am, um, a small business or a
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] creative agency, uh, and I have no idea about AI, um,
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] can you explain how to think about
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] the difference maybe between AI agents, workflows, what is an AI agent in
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] three words, and how a business can say, "Okay, here
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] we need this kind of thing. Here it's better. This, this other stuff." You know what I mean?
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] So...
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] In simple-
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] In- in simple words, maybe not three words, a little bit more.
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: audio_event] (laughs)
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] Uh, like 30 words, let's say.
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: audio_event] (laughs)
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] Okay, 30.
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] Um,
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] if I want to explain
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] what is an AI agent to my mother, that's how I will explain it.
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] Yeah.
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] An AI agent
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] is a software, um, that mimics the way
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] a human
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] performs tasks on a computer. That basically can work like the way a human can work on a
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] computer. There are different types of AI agents, the same way as there are different types of people using computers.
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] For example, there's a person
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] using Google Sheets doing accounting.
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] Uh, or there's a person using Google Docs.... writing, uh, documentation about something.
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] And that's how the AI agents can be different. And the, the most important part about AI agent is it
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] has like, why do we call it agent?
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] Yeah.
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] Because it has
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] agency. It can do things on its own. Um, the same way like James Bond, for example, if we take
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] James Bond as a connotation, um,
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] James Bond is an agent.
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] Okay.
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] He's a 007 A- agent, uh, of, um... Which country is it? US or, or British?
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] UK.
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] UK, British.
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] So, he goes and performs tasks in other co- uh, in other countries or in the same country, and then
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] he has tools, uh, that he
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] has, like a car that can drive and that can swim, that can fire, that can change the number plates.
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] That tool is important. So an AI agent
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] can have like a Google Sheet as a tool that can perform accounting tasks or can have a Gmail access
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] that can perform, um, an email com- composing an email. Uh, and, and then
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] James Bond has a very sharp memory. He can remember things. Uh, he can memorize things because he wants to
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] make sure that he can find the right criminal at the right time and then take it to the law.
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] And so is the case with an AI agent. An AI agent needs to kind of like remember things. For
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] example, if I ha- I have built an AI agent that
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] takes care of my email inbox
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] and I say that compose an email or send an email to John Doe and mention that I am gonna
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] be 20 minutes late, it should remember that who is John Doe
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] and where can I find his, his email address, and that's the memory part of an AI agent. So an
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] AI agent should have, uh, a memory, intelligence, agency, tools attached to that, and it should perform
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] tasks on your behalf based on fuzzy instructions in a natural language, whether this be chat or a voice or
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] connected to another system based on a trigger from another system. But it should have agency and it should learn
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] over time. Sorry, that was not three words or 30 words.
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: audio_event] (laughs)
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] I, I, I've never heard that, but I, I love the James Bond comparison. Now, I, I'm
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] building in my head a world around an AI agent like James Bond.
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] Yeah.
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] Yeah, it makes sense because like James Bonds receives from his boss, uh, like a goal-
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] ... like
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] find this criminal and kill him, let's say.
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: audio_event] (laughs)
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] Right? And it's something like that, right?
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] I hope he doesn't kill him and bring him to prison, but...
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: audio_event] (laughs)
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] Okay. Okay. Right. Let's say bring him to prison.
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] So you, you give the AI agent as well a goal, right?
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] Yes.
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] You can give it a goal and you give it tools, maybe an Excel, Google Sheet is not as cool
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] as James Bond car, but-
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] Yeah.
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] ... does the job. So he can then pick the right tools
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] in the order that the brain of the AI agent-
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] Yeah.
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] ... at the side, right? To reach a certain goal basically.
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] Yes.
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] Make sense?
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] We can, uh, do that kind of a connotation. I think, uh,
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] there must be a dozen more metaphors that we can come up with.
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] Yeah.
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] ChatGPT should help.
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: audio_event] (laughs)
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] Okay. Okay. That's, that's great. And so just to wrap it up, when, in which
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] situations, um, in the processing of a businesses, of a business, it makes sense to use
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] an agent with agency, as we said, or just a plain workflow that always do the same
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] steps?
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] So, um, if you have an, a workflow, better to be on n8n. Uh, if you have an n8n
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] workflow,
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] when to decide to put an AI agent or, or, or-
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] Yeah.
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] ... when to put, uh, AI capabilities in it,
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] eh, it will kind of like
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] become visible as soon as you start building it. If it's something to do with very
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] unclear inputs,
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] then most probably you need an AI agent node in n8n.
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] Mm-hmm.
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] For example, coming back to this receipt for this restaurant. Receipts can be scanned
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] and receipts can be of different types of data input. It already is indicating that it needs AI integration
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] because the amount of data that's coming in, the types of input is so much different.
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] And AI is very good in recognizing patterns and extracting text from
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] multiple different types of data input and then finding the right description for that invoice, the right date,
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] because one invoice or one receipt can have a date setting somewhere else, one in somewhere else. Um,
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] and extracting the amount, description, and so on. That is already an indication that you need an AI integration in
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] your workflow. But on the other side, if you want to have a workflow that is just like running
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] and doing something, it will li- automatically be identified because, for example, you have an API from one side, you're
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] sucking in all that data, you're sanitizing it, you're cleaning it, and you're dumping it in a, in a database.
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] In that case, you don't need AI because it's just like a pipeline that goes like from one, data flows
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] from one side, goes to the other side.
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] Mm-hmm.
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] So in that case, you don't need, uh, any AI integration.
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] Okay.
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] I think it's just the workflow when you start building it, it will identify itself that, oh, okay, here I,
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] I need AI. And then it's agentic and it's an AI automation. Uh, and, and gradually, it will
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] go to that AI agent world where it has at least this brain, the ChatGPT model, the, the, the
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] memory, and the tools. Those three basic
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] ingredients that makes an AI agent, an AI agent.
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] Mm-hmm. Okay. Yeah. So when the things are, yeah, not clear and usually need a human to decide what
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] to do, it's the right place
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] to, to use an AI agent, right?
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] Yes.
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] Yes. Okay.
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] Wonderful.
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: audio_event] (laughs)
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] Wonderful. I think we can
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] stop it here, right?
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] Wrap it up. Thank you so much.
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] And finish our beer. Thanks. Thanks to you.
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] Yeah. Thank you so much.
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] This was like random.
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] Yeah. Wait, wait a minute. Let's-
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] Yeah.
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] Let us, let us show you the, the-
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] ... the scene actually. Is it okay if we show the scene?
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] Yeah, sure.
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] Yeah, let's, let's go and s- show the scene. Where are we sitting? This is how we generate contents.
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: audio_event] (laughs)
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] So I learned from Amel today to just vibe code... no, vibe my content. And so we
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] randomly stopped here
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] and decided to-
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] Yeah.
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] ... to have a talk.
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] But take that stage.
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] Yeah.
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] That stage was so nice. And I think, uh, take, take this entire stage. Look at that. Like, if I,
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] if I-
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] It was made for it.
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] Yeah, it was literally waiting for us to, to take this stage-
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: audio_event] (laughs)
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] ... uh, and literally do this, uh, in a way that we did it. Thank you so much for the
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] interview.
[speaker_name | speaker_0 | types: word] Thanks, Amel.
[speaker_name | speaker_1 | types: word] It's a very nice content.